headwayapp.co 2019-12-20

# Headway - Changelog as a service. Simple as that.

## Privacy Policy

Your privacy is critically important to us. At Headway, we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don't ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can't stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don't share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don't store personal information on our servers unless required for the ongoing operation of one of our services.
  * We aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what's visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, or permanently deleted.

This privacy policy explains how we collect, use and disclose information about you when you use the services provided by **Headway App, Inc.** ("we", "us" or "our") via [headwayapp.co](https://headwayapp.co/) (collectively, the "Service").

Headwayapp operates [headwayapp.co](https://headwayapp.co/). It is Headway's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Headway collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Headway's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Headway's visitors use its website. From time to time, Headway may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. Headway also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users. Headway only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Headway choose to interact with Headway in ways that require Headway to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Headway gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Headway are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Headway collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Headway. Headway does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

Headway may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Headway may monitor the most liked and viewed entries. Headway may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Headway does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Headway discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Headway's behalf or to provide services available at Headway's website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Headway's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Headway will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Headway discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Headway believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Headway, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Headway website and have supplied your email address, Headway may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Headway and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Headway takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Headway uses cookies to help Headway identify and track visitors, their usage of Headway website, and their website access preferences. Headway visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Headway's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Headway's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If Headway, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Headway goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Headway may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Promotional Communications

You may opt out of receiving promotional emails or text messages from Headway by following the instructions in those emails or text messages. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional communications, such as those about your account or our ongoing business relations.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [hello@headwayapp.co](mailto:hello@headwayapp.co).

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Headway may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Headway's sole discretion. Headway encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
